New York State Public Employees Federation, AFL-CIO, Environmental Conservation Division (PEF/ENCON); Records apap114
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Committees, Programs, and Events, 1975-2000; 4; 3.54 cubic ft.
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Member Lists, 1988 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 36)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, News Clippings, 1985 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 37)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, News Clippings, Elizabeth Hoke, 1984 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 38)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, News Extra, 1983 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 39)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Newsletter Article Drafts, 1985 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 40)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Petition Drive, 1984 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 41)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Primary, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 42)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Primary, Committee for Independent Officers Materials, 1988 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 43)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Primary, Mailings, 1988 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 44)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Primary, Membership Lists, 1988 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 45)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Proposed PEF Constitution and By-Laws, 1979 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 46)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union / Pro-Member Team, Campaign, 1982 (Box 3 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 47)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union / Pro-Member Team, Campaign, 1985 (Box 4 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 1)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union / Pro-Member Team, Campaign, 1985 (Box 4 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 2)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union / Pro-Member Team, Campaign Literature, 1985 (Box 4 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 3)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union / Pro-Member Team, Election Victory Dinner, 1985 (Box 4 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 4)
  - Women's Advisory Program, By-Laws, 1995 (Box 4 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 5)
  - Women's Program, 1982 (Box 4 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 6)
  - Women's Program, Conference, 1982 (Box 4 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 7)
  - Women's Program, Conference, 1988; 1990 (Box 4 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 8)
  - Women's Program, Conference, 1991 (Box 4 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 9)
  - Women's Program, Conference, 1992 (Box 4 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 10)
  - Women's Program, Legislation, 1988 (Box 4 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 11)
  - Women's Program, Region 8, Events and Activities, 1983-1991 (Box 4 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 12)
  - Women's Program, Region 8, Meeting Minutes, 1983-1991 (Box 4 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 13)
  - Women's Program, Regional Conferences and Events, 1983-1986; 1990; 1993-1994 (Box 4 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 14)
  - AFT Convention, Progressive Caucus, 1984; 1986; 1988; 1990 (Box 5 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 1)
  - AFT Convention, United Action Caucus, 1984; 1986; 1988; 1990 (Box 5 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 2)
  - Hispanic Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 5 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 3)
  - New York State PEF Second Annual Convention, Rules, 1980 (Box 5 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 4)
  - Parking Committee, 1982-1987 (Box 5 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 5)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Election Certification, 1988 (Box 5 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 6)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Legal Issues with Executive Board, 1984 (Box 5 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 7)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, News Clippings, 1982-1984 (Box 5 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 8)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Platforms and Policies, 1988 (Box 5 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 9)
  - Unity Caucus, 1981 (Box 5 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 10)
  - Women's Program, 1983-1988 (Box 5 (4-Committees, Programs, and Events), Folder 11)
- Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1979-2000; 5; 2.5 cubic ft.
  This series contains materials posted by stewards on contract-mandated PEF bulletin boards at the Department of Environmental Conservation main offices in Albany. Included are a wide variety of materials of interest to PEF members, such as photocopies of correspondence on issues that affected members, news clippings of PEF and union-related articles, contract negotiation updates, and statewide union election information. There is also a great deal of information related to union activity at the local level, including political action events, local steward elections, and weekly steward meetings (including steward meeting attendance records).
  Although attempts have been made to maintain chronological order in this series, many items had no posting date. Some of these items were marked with a removal date, but it was often difficult to determine how long they had been posted prior to their removal.
  The series is mostly complete for the years 1979-2000; however, there are a few months for which there is no bulletin board material.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1979 April-1979 December (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 1)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1980 January-1980 June (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 2)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1980 July-1980 October (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 3)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1981 January-1981 April; 1981 June (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 4)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1981 July-1981 December (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 5)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1982 (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 6)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1983 January-1983 April (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 7)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1983 May-1983 December (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 8)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1984 January-1984 June (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 9)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1984 July-1984 December (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 10)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1985 January-1985 June (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 11)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1985 July-1985 December (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 12)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1986 January-1986 May (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 13)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1986 June-1986 December (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 14)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1987 January-1987 April (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 15)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1987 May-1987 August (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 16)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1987 September-1987 December (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 17)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1988 January-1988 March (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 18)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1988 April-1988 June (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 19)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1988 July-1988 September (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 20)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1988 October-1988 December (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 21)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1989 January-1989 March (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 22)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1989 April-1989 June (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 23)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1989 July-1989 August (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 24)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1989 September-1989 December (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 25)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1990 January-1990 March (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 26)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1990 April-1990 May (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 27)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1990 June; 1990 August (Box 1 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 28)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1990 September-1990 October (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 1)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1990 November-1990 December (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 2)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1991 January-1991 March (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 3)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1991 April-1991 June (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 4)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1991 July-1991 August (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 5)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1991 September (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 6)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1991 October-1991 December (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 7)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1992 January (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 8)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1992 February-1992 March (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 9)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1992 April-1992 June (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 10)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1992 July (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 11)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1992 August-1992 September (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 12)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1992 October-1992 November (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 13)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1992 December (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 14)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1993 January (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 15)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1993 February (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 16)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1993 March-1993 April (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 17)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1993 May-1993 June (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 18)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1993 July-1993 August (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 19)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1993 September-1993 December (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 20)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1994 January-1994 March (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 21)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1994 April-1994 June (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 22)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1994 July-1994 September (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 23)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1994 October-1994 December (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 24)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1995 January-1995 March (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 25)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1995 April-1995 June (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 26)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1995 July-1995 August; 1995 November (Box 2 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 27)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1996 January; 1996 April; 1996 May-1996 June (Box 3 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 1)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1996 July-1996 October (Box 3 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 2)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1996 November-1996 December (Box 3 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 3)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1997 January-1997 March (Box 3 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 4)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1997 July-1997 August (Box 3 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 5)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1997 April-1997 June (Box 3 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 6)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1997 September-1997 December (Box 3 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 7)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1998 February-1998 March (Box 3 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 8)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1998 April-1998 June (Box 3 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 9)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1998 July-1998 September (Box 3 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 10)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1998 October-1998 December (Box 3 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 11)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1999 January-1999 April (Box 3 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 12)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1999 May-1999 August (Box 3 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 13)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 1999 September-1999 December (Box 3 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 14)
  - Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings, 2000 January-2000 April (Box 3 (5-Division 169 Bulletin Board Postings), Folder 15)
- Publications, 1978-1999; 6; 2.73 cubic ft.
  This series consists of official PEF publications, as well as publications produced by other entities collected by PEF.
  Statewide PEF publications include The Communicator, PEF's official newspaper. The Communicator usually appeared monthly, although during some periods it was published semi-monthly. The run of The Communicator in this series is near-complete for the periods from 1979 through 1990 and from May 1994 through January 1999. There are numerous other statewide PEF publications as well, including Steward News, Contract Update, and newsletters for the women's and retirees' programs. In addition to these statewide publications, there are select issues of regional and divisional news publications.
  Non-PEF publications include newsletters produced by the New York Office of Employee Relations and the Civil Service Department.
  Statewide PEF publications are alphabetized by title. Publications produced by specific regions or divisions, as well as non-PEF publications, are alphabetized first by the name of the entity that produced them, then by title. There are several folders containing publications with more than one title - for example, the "Contracts Newsletter" folder and folders that contain newsletters from multiple regions and divisions. These folders are given titles that indicate the source of the publications.
  Committee or task force reports that were professionally printed for distribution are not included in this series. They can be found with the files of their respective creators in other series. For example, reports printed for PEF conventions are found in Series 4, under the heading of the convention at which they were distributed.
  Arranged alphabetically by publication, then chronologically.
  - Citizens' Environmental Coalition Toxics in Your Community Newsletter, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Civil Service Department, Newsletters, 1985-1990 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Coalition of Nurses in State Service, Newsletter, 1981 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Division 205 Pointers, 1985-1992 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Divisions, Newsletters, 1983-1988; 1990 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Emergency Committee to Save New York's Environment New York State Pipeline, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Health and Safety News, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Office of Employee Relations News, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Office of Employee Relations News, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Office of Employee Relations News, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Parole Officers Association News, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 11)
  - PEF Leader, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Regions 1, 3, 4, 7, 10, Newsletters, 1984-1988; 1991-1993 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Region 8 Heartland, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 14)
  - Retirement System Sentinel, 1992; 1993; 1999 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 15)
  - Retirement System Update, 1978-1990; 1994 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 16)
  - "This Is PEF", 1995 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 17)
  - United Steelworkers of America Local 9265 Union Scroll, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Contract Newsletters, 1981; 1984-1985; 1988; 1991; 1993 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Division 202 Union Bug, 1983-1989; 1991-1994 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Divisions, Newsletters, 1982-1986; 1988-1989; 1991; 1993; Undated (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Informed Membership Committee Membership Guardian, 1988; Undated (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Public Employees Merit Caucus The Uncivil Servant, 1983-1987 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Region 6, Newsletter, 1980-1991; Undated (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Retirees, Newsletter, 1981-1983; 1986; Undated (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union News and Views, 1980-1985; 1988 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Newsletter, 1979-1980 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Steward News, 1979-1981 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Steward News, 1982-1985 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 11)
  - Women's Program Newsletter, 1982-1984 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Workers' Compensation Board Newsletter, 1981 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 13)
  - New York State Believe It or Not, 1992 (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
  - New York State United Teachers, New York Teacher, 1984-1985 (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
  - Shop Talk, 1985-1989; 1992-1993 (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Newsletter, 1980-1984; 1986 (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
  - The Communicator, 1978-1981 (Oversized 2, Folder 1)
  - The Communicator, 1982-1985 (Oversized 2, Folder 2)
  - The Communicator, 1986-1987 (Oversized 2, Folder 3)
  - The Communicator, 1988 (Oversized 2, Folder 4)
  - The Communicator, 1989 January-1989 August (Oversized 2, Folder 5)
  - The Communicator, 1989 September-1989 December (Oversized 2, Folder 6)
  - The Communicator, 1990 January-1990 June (Oversized 2, Folder 7)
  - The Communicator, 1990 July-1990 December (Oversized 2, Folder 8)
  - The Communicator, 1994 May-1994 September (Oversized 3, Folder 1)
  - The Communicator, 1994 October-1994 December (Oversized 3, Folder 2)
  - The Communicator, 1995 January-1995 June (Oversized 3, Folder 3)
  - The Communicator, 1995 July-1995 December (Oversized 3, Folder 4)
  - The Communicator, 1996 January-1996 May (Oversized 3, Folder 5)
  - The Communicator, 1996 June-1996 December (Oversized 3, Folder 6)
  - The Communicator, 1997 February-1997 July (Oversized 3, Folder 7)
  - The Communicator, 1997 August-1997 December (Oversized 3, Folder 8)
  - The Communicator, 1998 January-1998 June (Oversized 3, Folder 9)
  - The Communicator, 1998 July-1999 January (Oversized 3, Folder 10)
- News Clippings, 1979-1999; 7; 0.5 cubic ft.
  News clippings appear throughout the collection in files relating to specific topics, particularly in Series 1, Series 2, and Series 4. This series consists of news clippings that were not organized by subject. Most were collected by PEF's central office for distribution within PEF, but some (particularly in later years) were collected by PEF/ENCON. In many cases, the letterhead onto which the clippings were photocopied indicate whether the clipping came from the central office or the ENCON division.
  News clippings include material about PEF itself, as well as material about other New York State labor unions and issues of interest to PEF and PEF/ENCON. The clippings come from a wide variety of newspapers and other periodicals; articles from the Albany Times Union, the Knickerbocker News, the Schenectady Gazette, and the New York Times appear most frequently. News articles, opinion pieces, and letters to the editor are all represented in this series.
  - News Clippings, 1979-1982 (Box 1 (7-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1983 January-1983 February (Box 1 (7-News Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1983 March (Box 1 (7-News Clippings), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1983 April (Box 1 (7-News Clippings), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1983 May-1983 June (Box 1 (7-News Clippings), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1983 July-1983 August (Box 1 (7-News Clippings), Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1983 September-1983 October (Box 1 (7-News Clippings), Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1983 November-1983 December (Box 1 (7-News Clippings), Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 1984 January (Box 1 (7-News Clippings), Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1984 February-1984 March (Box 2 (7-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1984 April-1984 May (Box 2 (7-News Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1984 June-1984 November (Box 2 (7-News Clippings), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1985-1993 (Box 2 (7-News Clippings), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1994-1999; Undated (Box 2 (7-News Clippings), Folder 5)
- Memorabilia, 1984-1985; 1988; 1999; Undated; 8; 0.2 cubic ft.
  This series consists of assorted memorabilia, including political campaign materials and convention materials. There are a variety of PEF stickers, promotional buttons, posters, a Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union T-shirt, a convention badge and backpack, and several other items.
  Arranged by format.
  - New York State PEF 21st Annual Convention, Membership Benefits Program Backpack, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Memorabilia), Folder 1)
  - New York State PEF 21st Annual Convention, Delegate Badge, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Memorabilia), Folder 2)
  - New York State Public Employees Federation, Assorted Stickers, 1988; Undated (Box 1 (8-Memorabilia), Folder 3)
  - New York State Public Employees Federation, Assorted Buttons, 1985; Undated (Box 1 (8-Memorabilia), Folder 4)
  - Mondale/Ferraro Campaign, Buttons, 1984 (Box 1 (8-Memorabilia), Folder 5)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, Buttons, 1985; Undated (Box 1 (8-Memorabilia), Folder 6)
  - United Steelworkers of America Local 9265, "Unionism Begins at Home" Hand-held Sign, Undated (Box 1 (8-Memorabilia), Folder 7)
  - Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union, T-Shirt, Undated (Box 1 (8-Memorabilia), Folder 8)